Nursing, School of; Records ua629
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative, 1966-1979; 2; 4.4 cubic ft.
  - R.N. Transitional Courses, NUR 100 and NUR 290, 1971-1973 (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 21)
  - Russell Sage College - Continuing Education Program Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 22)
  - School Census - RESTRICTED, 1967-1978 (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 23)
  - School of Nursing Self-Evaluation Report, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 24)
  - Search Committee for Dean of School of Nursing - RESTRICTED, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 25)
  - Self-Studies - RESTRICTED (1 of 2), 1972-1976; Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 26)
  - Self-Studies - RESTRICTED (2 of 2), 1972-1976; Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 27)
  - Space, School of Nursing, 1968-1971 (Box 4 (2-Administrative), Folder 28)
  - State Board Returns - RESTRICTED, 1971-1979; Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - State Education Department, Annual Reports, 1967-1979; Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - State Education Department, LPN License Applicants, 1972-1978 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - State Education Department, Site Visit Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Student-Faculty Ad Hoc Committee, Student Grievances and Involvement, 1969-1970; 1974-1977; Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Student-Faculty Liaison Committee Meeting Minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - Student-Faculty Liaison Committee Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Sub-Committee on Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - Summer Session, 1973-1976; 1978 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - SUNY Binghamton Project - RESTRICTED, 1969; 1974; 1976; Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - University Auxiliary Services, 1974-1979 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - Upper Division Council Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 5 (2-Administrative), Folder 12)
- Continuing Education, 1973-1979; 3; 4.0 cubic ft.
  Subseries 1 is arranged chronologically and Subseries 2 is arranged alphabetically.
  This series is divided into two subseries, one containing curricula of workshops and the other information about registrants. Please note that Series 2 of this collection also includes a general administrative file on continuing education and one on tranferring the continuing education program to Russell Sage College in 1979 upon closure of the School of Nursing.
  - Workshop Curriculum, 1973 March 12-1979 June 13; 3.1; 1.4 cubic ft.
    Arranged chronologically.
    This sub-series of the Continuing Education series contains curricula for the workshops starting in March of 1973 until June of 1979. Files include agendas, correspondence, workshop participant lists, suggested readings, worksheets and other teaching materials, and participant feedback. Topics ranged from nursing and law to drug therapy to elder care.
    - Planning Nursing Care for the Aged, 1973 March 12-14; 1973 June 6; 1973 September 19; 1973 November 14; 1974 February 18-19 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 1)
    - Trends in Healthcare Services, 1973 April 3 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 2)
    - Designing an Effective In-service Program, 1973 June 20-22 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 3)
    - Planning: A Necessity for Effective Administration, 1973 June 25-27 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 4)
    - The Nurse and the Law - RESTRICTED, 1973 September 22 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 5)
    - Physiology Cardiopulmonary Systems, 1973 October 11- 12 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 6)
    - Identification and Use of Resources in Nursing Service, 1973 October 30; 1973 November 1-2 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 7)
    - The Nursing Audit, 1973 November 28-30 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 8)
    - The Art of Communication as a Nursing Service Administrator, 1974 February 13- 15 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 9)
    - The Process in Restorative Nursing, 1974 March 28- 29 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 10)
    - Methods of Teaching Inservice Education, 1974 April 25-26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 11)
    - The Nursing Service Director's Responsibility for Staff Development, 1974 May 15-17 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 12)
    - Physiology: Applied to Nursing Practice, 1974 June 3-4 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 13)
    - Methods of Teaching in Inservice Education, 1974 July 18-19 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 14)
    - Problem Oriented Patient Record, 1974 September 19-20 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 15)
    - Legal Aspects of Nursing, 1974 October 19 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 16)
    - Nursing Audit, 1974 October 21-23 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 17)
    - Nursing Process, 1974 November 14-15 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 18)
    - Peer Review, 1974 May 12 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 19)
    - Taking Responsibility for Quality Nursing Care, 1975 February 27-28 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 20)
    - Introduction to Physical Assessment of the Adult, 1975 March 26-27 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 21)
    - The Role of the Nurse in Crisis Intervention, 1975 April 3 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 22)
    - The Function of Planning an Inservice Education Program, 1975 April 29-30 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 23)
    - The Physiology of the Nervous System as Applied to General Nursing Practice, 1975 June 2-3 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 24)
    - Improving Nursing Skills in Working with Diabetic Patients, 1975 June 19-20 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 25)
    - Planning and Implementing the Nursing Service Budget, 1975 June 25-27 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 26)
    - Nursing Care Plans - The Why's and Therefore's, 1975 July 1-2 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 27)
    - Introduction to Physical Assessment of the Adult, 1975 July 15-16 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 28)
    - Methods of Teaching in Inservice Education, 1975 July 16-17 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 29)
    - Legal Aspects of Nursing Practice, 1975 September 13 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 30)
    - Supervision in Community Health, 1975 September 24-26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 31)
    - Improving Communication Skills in the Nursing Process, 1975 October 21-22 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 32)
    - The Function of Planning in Inservice Education Program, 1975 November 20-21 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 33)
    - Toward More Understanding of Aging and Dying, 1976 January 31 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 34)
    - Writing Behavioral Objectives, 1976 February 5-6 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 35)
    - Nursing Care Plans: The Why's and Therefore's, 1976 March 3-4 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 36)
    - Improving Communication Skills in the Nursing Process, 1976 April 13-14 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 37)
    - The Nurse's Responsibility in Drug Therapy, 1976 April 21-28; 1976 May 12-19 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 38)
    - Negotiating and Living with a Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1976 May 20-21 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 39)
    - Nursing Supervision in Long Term Care Settings, 1976 June 16-17 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 40)
    - Performance Evaluation, 1976 July 7-8 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 41)
    - Law and Modern Nursing Practice, 1976 September 18 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 42)
    - Nurse's Responsibility in Drug Therapy, 1976 September 29; 1976 October 6 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 43)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 44)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, Final Expenditure Report, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 45)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, Narrative Report, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 46)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, Participant Evaluation Forms, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 47)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, Public Announcement, Program Content, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 48)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, Request from VEA to SUNY Albany, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 49)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, VEA, IFR, Budget Data, Approval, etc., 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 50)
    - Teaching Newer Concepts of Nursing Care for the Aged, VEA Proposal, 1976 October 2-1977 March 26 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 51)
    - Performance Evaluation, 1976 November 17-18 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 52)
    - Use of the Problem-Oriented Record in Psychiatric Patient Care, 1977 January 19-20 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 53)
    - Performance Evaluation, 1977 February 17-18 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 54)
    - Nurse Teaching - Patient Learning, 1977 March 30-31 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 55)
    - Nursing Care of the Elderly, 1977 April 14-15 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 56)
    - Nursing Assessment, 1977 June 29-30 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 57)
    - Methods of Teaching Inservice Education, 1977 July 7-8 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 58)
    - Performance Evaluation, 1977 August 3-4 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 59)
    - Legal Aspects of Modern Nursing Practice, 1977 September 10 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 60)
    - Use of Values Clarification in Nursing, 1977 October 10 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 61)
    - Negotiating and Living with a Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1977 October 26-27 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 62)
    - Primary Nursing, 1977 November 10 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 63)
    - Nurse Teaching - Patient Learning, 1977 December 1-2 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 64)
    - Changing Responsibilities of Nursing Service Administration: Accent on Accountability, 1978 January 25 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 65)
    - Designing a Competency Based Staff Education Program, 1978 February 2-3 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 66)
    - Problem Oriented Charting, 1978 February 24 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 67)
    - Skin Integrity in the Older Adult, 1978 March 14 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 68)
    - Nursing Management of Pain, 1978 March 29-30 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 69)
    - Workshop on Management for Supervisors, Charge Nurses, and Coordinators, 1978 April 13-14 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 1)
    - Using and Evaluating Nursing Care Plans, 1978 May 3-4 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 2)
    - Nursing Care of the Elderly, 1978 May 11-12 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 3)
    - Nurse Teaching - Patient Learning, 1978 June 22-23 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 4)
    - Primary Nursing, 1978 July 14 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 5)
    - Developing Cost Effective Self-Learning Packages, 1978 August 2-3 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 6)
    - Methods of Teaching Inservice Education, 1978 September 19-20 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 7)
    - Group Leadership Skills for Nurses, 1978 October 12-13 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 8)
    - Workshop on Management for Supervisors, Charge Nurses, and Coordinators, 1978 October 30-31 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 9)
    - Staffing and Budgeting, 1978 November 16-17 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 10)
    - Legal Implications of Professional Nursing Practice, 1978 December 8 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 11)
    - Using and Evaluating Nursing Care Plans, 1979 February 7-8 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 12)
    - Methods of Teaching Inservice Education, 1979 February 14-15 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 13)
    - Workshop on Management for Supervisors, Charge Nurses, and Coordinators, 1979 March 21-22 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 14)
    - Use of Computers and Doing Research, 1979 April 5-6 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 15)
    - The Role of the Nurse in Crisis Intervention, 1979 April 17 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 16)
    - Nursing Care of the Elderly, 1979 May 9-10 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 17)
    - Workshop on Management for Supervisors, Charge Nurses, and Coordinators, 1979 June 4-5 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 18)
    - Methods of Teaching Inservice Education, 1979 June 12-13 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 19)
  - Workshop Registrations, 1973-1979; 3.2; 2.6 cubic ft.
    This sub-series of the Continuing Education series consists of the registration materials of workshop participants. As the files contain sensitive personal information, the entire sub-series is restricted. The School of Nursing kept all registration material alphabetically, regardless of the date of the respective workshop. One file at the end of the series includes an alphabetical list of all participants from all workshops from 1973-1979.
    - A - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 1)
    - Ba - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 2)
    - Be - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 3)
    - Bi-Bl - RESTRICTED, 1974-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 4)
    - Bo - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 5)
    - Br - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 6)
    - Bu - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 7)
    - Ca - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 8)
    - Ce - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 9)
    - Co - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 10)
    - Cr-Cu - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 11)
    - Da - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 12)
    - De-Di - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 13)
    - Do-Dr - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 14)
    - E - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 15)
    - Fa-Fi - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 16)
    - Fl - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 17)
    - Ga - RESTRICTED, 1973-1975; 1977-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 18)
    - Ge-Gl - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 19)
    - Go-Gu - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 20)
    - Ha - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 21)
    - He - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 22)
    - Hi-Ho - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 1)
    - Hr-Hy - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 2)
    - I - RESTRICTED, 1974-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 3)
    - J - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 4)
    - Ka-Ke - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 5)
    - Ki-Kw - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 6)
    - La-Le - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 7)
    - Li - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 8)
    - Ma - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 9)
    - Mac - RESTRICTED, 1973-1978 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 10)
    - Mc - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 11)
    - Mi - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 12)
    - Mo - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 13)
    - Mu - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 14)
    - N - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 15)
    - O - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 16)
    - Pa - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 17)
    - Pe - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 18)
    - Pl - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 19)
    - Q - RESTRICTED, 1974-1978 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 20)
    - Ra - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 21)
    - Ri - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 22)
    - Ro - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 23)
    - Ru - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 24)
    - Sa - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 25)
    - Se - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 1)
    - Si - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 2)
    - Sn - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 3)
    - St - RESTRICTED, 1974-1979; Undated (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 4)
    - Su - RESTRICTED, 1974-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 5)
    - Ta - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 6)
    - Ti - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 7)
    - U & V - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 8)
    - Wa - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 9)
    - We - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 10)
    - Wi - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 11)
    - Wo - RESTRICTED, 1974-1979 (Box 4 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 1)
    - Y & Z - RESTRICTED, 1973-1979 (Box 4 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 2)
    - Workshop Participants by Name - RESTRICTED, ca. 1979 (Box 4 (3-Continuing Education), Folder 3)
- General Subject Files, 1964-1979; 4; 0.8 cubic ft.
  The Subject Files series contains a variety of materials such as files on the history of the School of Nursing, convocation, newspaper clippings and alumni and graduate surveys.
  - Alumni Association, 1971; 1977 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Surveys (folder 1/4) - RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Surveys (folder 2/4) - RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Alumni Surveys (folder 3/4) - RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Alumni Surveys (folder 4/4) - RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Beta Beta Beta (Biology Honorary) - RESTRICTED, 1970; 1977; Undated (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Christine Sturtevant Award, 1974-1976; 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Community-University Day Programs, School of Nursing, 1972-1973; 1975; 1977 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Convocation, 1971-1979 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Design of School of Nursing Pin and Pinette, 1971 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Graduate Survey, 1975-1976; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - History-Faculty, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - History-Funding - RESTRICTED, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - History-News Releases, 1964; 1967-1968; 1970; 1972-1976; Undated (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - History of School-Space Development, 1965; 1968; 1970; Undated (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Inventory List, Furniture, 1967-1968; 1974; 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Inventory List, Instructional Resources, 1977; 1979; Undated (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Requests from Com. Agenc. or Individual, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Resolution, Conferral of the Bachelor of Science Degree in Nursing, 1973 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - School of Nursing Blank Certificate, Undated (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - School of Nursing Brochures, 1967; 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - School of Nursing Yearbook, 1979 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - State Education Program, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Student Nurses Organization Events, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Students of Nursing Organizations, 1971; 1974; 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - SUNY Annual Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Transactions within the University, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Transactions with SUNY-Central, 1966 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Written Histories of the School of Nursing, 1971-1979 (Box 2 (4-General Subject Files), Folder 16)